{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768680113","data":{"timestamp":" 947768680113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" fa4079f0-cdf1-4728-8f21-07d38f772306"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768685050","data":{"timestamp":" 947768685050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" fa4079f0-cdf1-4728-8f21-07d38f772306"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768692149","data":{"timestamp":" 947768692149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" fa4079f0-cdf1-4728-8f21-07d38f772306"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768692956","data":{"timestamp":" 947768692956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" fa4079f0-cdf1-4728-8f21-07d38f772306"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768701611","data":{"timestamp":" 947768701611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768701833","data":{"timestamp":" 947768701833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768702808","data":{"timestamp":" 947768702807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768704091","data":{"timestamp":" 947768704090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768707030","data":{"timestamp":" 947768707029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768707873","data":{"timestamp":" 947768707873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768708185","data":{"timestamp":" 947768708185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768709418","data":{"timestamp":" 947768709418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768712907","data":{"timestamp":" 947768712906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768713901","data":{"timestamp":" 947768713901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768714163","data":{"timestamp":" 947768714163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768715113","data":{"timestamp":" 947768715112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768718024","data":{"timestamp":" 947768718023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768719066","data":{"timestamp":" 947768719065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768719547","data":{"timestamp":" 947768719546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768724107","data":{"timestamp":" 947768724106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768724199","data":{"timestamp":" 947768724199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 2a35cd2a-dae6-4494-8e84-568dee35ba30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768742964","data":{"timestamp":" 947768742964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 7ab991aa-721a-4df9-ad86-a05c8288a1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ze-vo-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768745505","data":{"timestamp":" 947768745504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 7ab991aa-721a-4df9-ad86-a05c8288a1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ze-vo-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768801753","data":{"timestamp":" 947768801753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 7ab991aa-721a-4df9-ad86-a05c8288a1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ze-vo-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768812904","data":{"timestamp":" 947768812904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768813298","data":{"timestamp":" 947768813297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768813540","data":{"timestamp":" 947768813540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768813863","data":{"timestamp":" 947768813863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768814107","data":{"timestamp":" 947768814107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768817582","data":{"timestamp":" 947768817582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768817881","data":{"timestamp":" 947768817880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768818795","data":{"timestamp":" 947768818795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768819229","data":{"timestamp":" 947768819228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768822207","data":{"timestamp":" 947768822206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768822506","data":{"timestamp":" 947768822506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768823360","data":{"timestamp":" 947768823360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768824036","data":{"timestamp":" 947768824036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768824784","data":{"timestamp":" 947768824783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768825121","data":{"timestamp":" 947768825120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768825406","data":{"timestamp":" 947768825405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768825731","data":{"timestamp":" 947768825731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768826002","data":{"timestamp":" 947768826002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768829747","data":{"timestamp":" 947768829746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768830138","data":{"timestamp":" 947768830137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768830382","data":{"timestamp":" 947768830381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768830705","data":{"timestamp":" 947768830705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768830952","data":{"timestamp":" 947768830951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768834394","data":{"timestamp":" 947768834394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768834687","data":{"timestamp":" 947768834686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768835598","data":{"timestamp":" 947768835597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768836030","data":{"timestamp":" 947768836030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768838960","data":{"timestamp":" 947768838960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768839250","data":{"timestamp":" 947768839250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768840102","data":{"timestamp":" 947768840101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768840778","data":{"timestamp":" 947768840778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768841525","data":{"timestamp":" 947768841524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768841855","data":{"timestamp":" 947768841855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768842142","data":{"timestamp":" 947768842142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768842465","data":{"timestamp":" 947768842465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768842744","data":{"timestamp":" 947768842743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768846212","data":{"timestamp":" 947768846209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768846333","data":{"timestamp":" 947768846332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768854117","data":{"timestamp":" 947768854116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" d9afaffc-085d-4c61-ae9b-f8b0c0b7b039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768880543","data":{"timestamp":" 947768880543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_zi-vyu-cha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768920837","data":{"timestamp":" 947768920837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_bwe-ro-cha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768926028","data":{"timestamp":" 947768926028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768936003","data":{"timestamp":" 947768936003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768948223","data":{"timestamp":" 947768948223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768955716","data":{"timestamp":" 947768955715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768974744","data":{"timestamp":" 947768974744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768988867","data":{"timestamp":" 947768988867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947768994769","data":{"timestamp":" 947768994769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769003507","data":{"timestamp":" 947769003507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769012183","data":{"timestamp":" 947769012183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" ce78ec97-248e-438b-8a98-2960ece131f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_cha..cha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cha_cha-nu-mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769051380","data":{"timestamp":" 947769051380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 1d5a09bc-bbc0-4632-a532-b939de9f7644"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769056985","data":{"timestamp":" 947769056985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 1d5a09bc-bbc0-4632-a532-b939de9f7644"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769061651","data":{"timestamp":" 947769061651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 1d5a09bc-bbc0-4632-a532-b939de9f7644"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769069225","data":{"timestamp":" 947769069225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 1d5a09bc-bbc0-4632-a532-b939de9f7644"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769077635","data":{"timestamp":" 947769077635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 1d5a09bc-bbc0-4632-a532-b939de9f7644"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769080696","data":{"timestamp":" 947769080696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 1d5a09bc-bbc0-4632-a532-b939de9f7644"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769088928","data":{"timestamp":" 947769088928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769089151","data":{"timestamp":" 947769089151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769090114","data":{"timestamp":" 947769090113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769091387","data":{"timestamp":" 947769091387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769094245","data":{"timestamp":" 947769094245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769095088","data":{"timestamp":" 947769095088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769095401","data":{"timestamp":" 947769095401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769096634","data":{"timestamp":" 947769096634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769100097","data":{"timestamp":" 947769100097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769101079","data":{"timestamp":" 947769101079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769101333","data":{"timestamp":" 947769101333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769102276","data":{"timestamp":" 947769102276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769105081","data":{"timestamp":" 947769105081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769106114","data":{"timestamp":" 947769106114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769106587","data":{"timestamp":" 947769106587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769110168","data":{"timestamp":" 947769110168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769110248","data":{"timestamp":" 947769110248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769115937","data":{"timestamp":" 947769115936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769124272","data":{"timestamp":" 947769124272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769131499","data":{"timestamp":" 947769131499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769139687","data":{"timestamp":" 947769139686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769164968","data":{"timestamp":" 947769164967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769173287","data":{"timestamp":" 947769173287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769181308","data":{"timestamp":" 947769181308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769189642","data":{"timestamp":" 947769189641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 33e355ea-7f40-43f8-8e59-0d74e905da75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769216899","data":{"timestamp":" 947769216899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-li-shu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769239738","data":{"timestamp":" 947769239738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mza-mgo-nye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769249750","data":{"timestamp":" 947769249750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_wi-nye-mwo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769259679","data":{"timestamp":" 947769259679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_te-nye-vye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769264799","data":{"timestamp":" 947769264799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-yo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" vyu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769270176","data":{"timestamp":" 947769270176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-yo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769277940","data":{"timestamp":" 947769277940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nde-mre-nye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769282399","data":{"timestamp":" 947769282399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-ra-ye"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769290792","data":{"timestamp":" 947769290792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-ha-two"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769298809","data":{"timestamp":" 947769298809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-mmo-nge"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769305381","data":{"timestamp":" 947769305381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mke-nu-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769311102","data":{"timestamp":" 947769311102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mke-nu-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769318599","data":{"timestamp":" 947769318599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" dc34cca6-11f4-4da9-bfbf-eef523f0dcec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.show.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mke-nu-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769332929","data":{"timestamp":" 947769332928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mto-nye-mwu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769337831","data":{"timestamp":" 947769337831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_sa-nye-vye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769345380","data":{"timestamp":" 947769345380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mji-pi-nye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769358112","data":{"timestamp":" 947769358112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_va-nye-mja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769364545","data":{"timestamp":" 947769364545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_ha-nye-chi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769370342","data":{"timestamp":" 947769370342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_ha-nye-chi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769377983","data":{"timestamp":" 947769377983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_we-mmo-nye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769392175","data":{"timestamp":" 947769392175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-yi-nu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769410348","data":{"timestamp":" 947769410348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" 9e7f77c4-73b0-4cac-a4fc-3599a380d9d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mju-nye-he"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769495693","data":{"timestamp":" 947769495693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mo-nye-ge"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769501440","data":{"timestamp":" 947769501440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mo-nye-ge"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769505637","data":{"timestamp":" 947769505636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_nye-yi-nu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769512329","data":{"timestamp":" 947769512329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mto-nye-mwu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769520802","data":{"timestamp":" 947769520802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_sa-nye-vye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769527902","data":{"timestamp":" 947769527902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mji-pi-nye"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769532207","data":{"timestamp":" 947769532207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_ha-nye-chi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769539843","data":{"timestamp":" 947769539843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_va-nye-mja"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769544403","data":{"timestamp":" 947769544403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mju-nye-he"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769549898","data":{"timestamp":" 947769549898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_mpi-tu-nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769583868","data":{"timestamp":" 947769583868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_we-mmo-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nye"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769589687","data":{"timestamp":" 947769589686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_160423"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_we-mmo-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}